<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_result_detail">ResultDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search for a player</string>

    <string name="mainAppTitleTV">Kwon Fantasy Football</string>
    <string name="mainFantasyRosterTitleTV">ROSTER-1</string>
    <string name="mainFantasyRoster2TitleTV">ROSTER-2</string>
    <string name="mainSearchResultsTitleTV">PLAYERS</string>

    <string name="toastPlayerDuplicate">Player already on roster!</string>
    <string name="toastPositionTaken">Position already taken!</string>
    <string name="toastRemovePlayerInstructions">Player added! Long-click to remove</string>
    <string name="toastPlayerRemoved">Player removed from roster</string>
    <string name="toastResetRoster">Roster reset!</string>
    <string name="toastResetSearch">List reset!</string>

    <string name="alertDialogTitle">Current Roster</string>
    <string name="alertDialogBackButton">Go back to Player Details</string>

    <string name="googleSearchString">http://www.google.com/search?q=Season stats for</string>
    <string name="GoogleSearchButton">Check Stats</string>

    <string name="CheckRosterButton">Check Roster</string>

    <string name="posQB">QB</string>
    <string name="posWR">WR</string>
    <string name="posRB">RB</string>

    <string name="teamNE">New England Patriots</string>
    <string name="teamCAR">Carolina Panthers</string>
    <string name="teamNYJ">New York Jets</string>
    <string name="teamDEN">Denver Broncos</string>
    <string name="teamROC">Rochester Yellowjackets</string>
    <string name="teamTB">Tampa Bay Buccaneers</string>
    <string name="teamPIT">Pittsburgh Steelers</string>
    <string name="teamLAR">Los Angeles Rams</string>
    <string name="teamMIN">Minnesota Vikings</string>


    <string name="TomBradyBio">Thomas Edward Patrick Brady, Jr. (born August 3, 1977) is an American football quarterback
        for the New England Patriots of the National Football League (NFL). After playing college football for the University of Michigan,
        Tom Brady was drafted by the Patriots in the sixth round of the 2000 NFL draft. In Bradys 13 full seasons as a starter
        (he missed nearly all of 2008 with a torn ACL),the Patriots have earned six trips to the Super Bowl, winning four.
        Brady has won three Super Bowl MVP awards, two league MVP awards (2007, 2010), has been selected to eleven Pro Bowls, and has
        led the Patriots to more division titles than any other quarterback in NFL history, with thirteen. Brady is fifth on the all-time
        list for career passing yards and third for career touchdown passes. His career postseason record is 22–9; his playoff win total
        is the most in NFL history. He helped set the record for the longest consecutive win streak in NFL history with 21 straight wins
        over two seasons (2003–2004). He also set the record for most consecutive playoff wins with 10, and in 2007 led the Patriots to the
        first undefeated regular season since the institution of the 16-game schedule. He has thrown for more passing yards and touchdowns
        than any quarterback in NFL postseason history, and has the sixth highest career passer rating of all time (96.6) among quarterbacks
        with at least 1,500 career passing attempts.</string>
    <string name="PeytonBio">Peyton Williams Manning (born March 24, 1976) is an American football quarterback for the Denver Broncos
        of the National Football League (NFL). A five-time league MVP, he played for the Indianapolis Colts for 14 seasons between 1998
        and 2011. He is a son of former NFL quarterback Archie Manning and an elder brother of New York Giants quarterback Eli Manning.
        Manning played college football for the University of Tennessee, leading the Volunteers to the 1997 SEC Championship
        in his senior season. He was chosen by the Indianapolis Colts with the first overall pick in the 1998 NFL Draft. Mannings playing
        career and statistics have ranked him among the greatest passing quarterbacks of all-time. From 1998 to 2010, he led the
        Indianapolis Colts to eight (seven AFC South and one AFC East) division championships, two AFC championships, and one Super Bowl
        championship (Super Bowl XLI). His five NFL MVPs are a league record, he was the most valuable player of Super Bowl XLI,
        has been named to 14 Pro Bowls, has thirteen 4,000-yard passing seasons, and is the Indianapolis Colts all-time leader
        in passing yards (54,828) and touchdown passes (399). In 2009, he was named the best player in the NFL,[3][4] and Fox Sports,
        along with Sports Illustrated, named him the NFL player of the decade for the 2000s. Before the 2013 season had even finished,
        SI had named him their Sportsman of the Year.</string>
    <string name="CamBio">Cameron Jerrell Newton (born May 11, 1989) is an American football player who is the quarterback for
        the Carolina Panthers of the National Football League (NFL). He played college football at Auburn and was drafted as the
        first overall pick by the Panthers in the 2011 NFL Draft. Newton is the only player in the modern era to, within a one-year
        span, be awarded the Heisman Trophy, win a national championship, and become the first overall pick in an NFL draft.
        He was the 2011 NFL Rookie of the Year, is a 3 time Pro Bowler, and was named to the NFL All Pro First Team in 2015.
        In his rookie year, Newton broke numerous rookie and all-time NFL records for passing and rushing yards. He became the
        first NFL quarterback to throw for 400 yards in his first game, shattering Peyton Mannings first-game record by 120 yards.
        He also broke Otto Grahams 61-year-old record for passing yards by any quarterback in an NFL debut. Newton would go on
        to become the first rookie quarterback to throw for 4,000 yards in a season, as well as the first rookie quarterback to
        rush for 700 yards. He also ran for 14 touchdowns, more in a single season than any quarterback in NFL history, breaking
        Steve Grogans 35-year-old record. In 2015, Newton became the first quarterback in NFL history to throw for 30 touchdowns
        and rush for 10 in the same season (35 passing, 10 rushing). He also became the only quarterback ever to have 300 yards
        passing, 5 touchdown passes, and over 100 yards rushing in the same game. In the final game of the 2015–16 season Newton
        tied Steve Youngs record for the most career rushing touchdowns by a quarterback—a record that Young set after 15 seasons
        in the NFL, compared to Newtons five.</string>
    <string name="KwonBio">Michael Kwon (born Oct 15, 1983) is a student in General Assembly\'s Android Development Immersive.
        He played Wide Receiver at the University of Rochester many, many, many, many, many years ago.  These days, he spends
        his time coding, drinking too much coffee, and being a bro.</string>
    <string name="AntonioBio">Antonio Brown (born July 10, 1988) is an American football wide receiver, and a punt returner
        for the Pittsburgh Steelers of the National Football League (NFL). He was drafted by the Steelers in the sixth round
        of the 2010 NFL Draft. He played college football at Central Michigan, where he was named a first-team All-American
        by The Sporting News as a punt returner in 2008 and 2009. In his junior year, Brown hauled in 110 receptions for 1,498
        yards and 9 touchdowns while helping lead the Central Michigan Chippewas to their second Mid-American Conference championship
        in three years and a Top 25 finish in the nation in the final January 2010 AP Poll and USA Today Coaches Poll.</string>
    <string name="BrandonBio">Brandon Tyrone Marshall (born March 23, 1984) is an American football wide receiver for the New York
        Jets of the National Football League (NFL). He played college football at Central Florida, and was drafted by the Denver Broncos
        in the fourth round of the 2006 NFL Draft. Marshall has also played for the Miami Dolphins and Chicago Bears. Marshall is known
        for his ability to break and dodge tackles. He led all NFL wide receivers in yards after first contact for the 2007 NFL
        season. Regarding Marshalls breakaway ability, cornerback Brandon Flowers said, "Brandon Marshall is a defensive lineman
        playing wide receiver. He wants to inflict punishment on you. He wants you to try to tackle him so he can shove you off of him
        and get more yards." Cornerback Nnamdi Asomugha said Marshall is "the toughest guy to bring down, one-on-one." On December
        13, 2009, Marshall set an NFL record for receptions in a game with 21. He also is one of only five players in NFL history
        to catch at least 100 passes in three consecutive seasons.
    </string>
    <string name="APBio">Adrian Lewis Peterson (born March 21, 1985) is an American football running back for the Minnesota Vikings
        of the National Football League (NFL). He was drafted by the Vikings seventh overall in the 2007 NFL Draft. He played
        college football at Oklahoma. Peterson set the NCAA freshman rushing record with 1,925 yards as a true freshman during the
        2004 season. As a unanimous first-team All-American, he became the first freshman to finish as the runner-up in the Heisman
        Trophy balloting. Peterson finished his college football career as the Sooners third all-time leading rusher. Following his
        first pro season, in which he set an NFL record for most rushing yards in a single game (296), Peterson was named the NFL
        Offensive Rookie of the Year. He was then awarded the MVP award for his performance in the Pro Bowl and became only the
        fifth player in NFL history to have more than 3,000 yards through his first two seasons. In 2010, he became the fifth fastest
        player to run for 5,000 yards, doing so in his 51st game. In 2012, Peterson became the sixth fastest player to reach 8,000
        rushing yards, ending the season with 2,097 rushing yards, just nine yards shy of breaking Eric Dickersons single season
        all-time record. Peterson amassed 2,314 all-purpose yards from scrimmage in 2012, tying Marcus Allen for the eighth-highest
        total ever. For his efforts, he received the NFL MVP Award and the AP NFL Offensive Player of the Year Award for the 2012
        NFL season. Peterson also achieved the #1 spot on the NFL Networks Top 100 Players of 2013. During the 2013 season,
        Peterson became the third fastest player to reach 10,000 rushing yards in NFL history.</string>
    <string name="DougBio">Douglas Matthew Baranco Martin (born January 13, 1989) is an American football running back for the
        Tampa Bay Buccaneers of the National Football League (NFL). Martin was born in Oakland, California, in 1989 and grew up
        in Stockton, California, where he attended St. Mary High School. He was a letterman in football and track. As a junior,
        Martin rushed 228 times for 1,950 yards and 18 touchdowns, earning first- team all-selection and all-area honors by the
        Stockton Record and All-San Joaquin accolades by Comcast Sports. During his senior season, Martin rushed for 1,234 yards
        on 171 carries and 14 touchdowns winning the teams MVP award. Martin attended Boise State University from 2007 to 2011.
        He finished his career with 3,431 yards on 617 carries with 43 touchdowns. The Tampa Bay Buccaneers selected Martin with
        the 31st overall pick of the 2012 NFL Draft, making him the first player from Boise State University to be drafted by the
        Buccaneers. On June 4, 2012, Martin signed a 5-year contract, worth $6.787 million with the team. After a successful 2012
        preseason with the Buccaneers, where he rushed for 97 yards on 27 carries to go with 2 rushing touchdowns, Martin was
        officially named as the starting running back entering the 2012 regular season by coach Greg Schiano.</string>
    <string name="GurleyBio">Todd Gurley II (born August 3, 1994) is an American football running back for the Los Angeles Rams
        of the National Football League (NFL). He was drafted by the Rams tenth overall in the 2015 NFL draft. He played college
        football at Georgia. Gurley attended Tarboro High School in Tarboro, North Carolina, where he was a three-sport star in
        football, track and basketball. He played as a running back and defensive back during his junior season, totalling 1,472
        rushing yards and 26 touchdowns, as well as 79 tackles, an interception, and a forced fumble. He was named Rocky Mount
        Telegram All-Area Offensive Player of the Year for the 2010 season. As a senior in 2011, he was the North Carolina Associated
        Press Player of the Year after totalling 2,600 yards and 38 touchdowns. Gurley helped his team win the 2A North Carolina
        state championship, rushing for 242 yards and four touchdowns in the championship game against Northside High School.
        In the semifinals, Northside had shut down the states leading rusher, Northsides Shaquan Johnson, who entered the game with
        3,083 rushing yards.</string>
</resources>
